Yuki sends a message to Fushi by the means of a clay pot.
The entity who created the rule that is Fushi.
Destroy that, then the mystery behind Fushi's life may finally be solved.
Damn it!
I'll show him! I will do it!
Fushi takes a different approach and asks a certain human for help.
The culmination of the alumnus leaves mouth in the end
Don't need help too.
So is it that Did you direct me to F Cannon?
Why should I be 이제 I am in this kernel?
The end of the world is nothing new or the PU.
It's necessary for full time withoutrendost work
終わらない想いを繰り返し 秘密の彼方へ
不安から遠ざかる術は どこにあるのか見えないまま
誰かが変わってくれたなら それで救われるのか
I want to sing the song
I want to sing the words and the words
I want to sing the secret to the world
Hey, can you tell me which cita is mine again?
Huh? Oh, um, it's right there
Ah, thanks
Hey, Mizuha
Is there anything you need?
I'll help you any way I can
See, I told you
She's coming
Uh, do you really think it's strange
Seeing Mizuha and I getting along together?
No, why are you asking?
You never said anything
You know what?
I think we should all go on a date together
You three, me, and Mizuha
And that way, we can become even better friends
Let's go
Think about it, okay?
Buna
Why weren't you at practice this morning?
You had me worried
Don't harm me
Are you all right?
You've been acting different lately
I don't see you with Saki and the others
Has something happened?
Yeah, I guess things are a little weird
Oh, did you have a fight?
I don't know how to get any closer to them
They run away before we can even talk
I get it
Well, those three always stick together
Because it makes them feel stronger that way
Try talking to them one-on-one
I'm sure they'll be different
I see
Good idea
You can thank me by coming back to club
Everyone misses you there, you know
Please, just don't forget that there are people out there
Who are worried about you, Funa
Even if they don't say it, okay?
Saki!
Hey, bestie!
So, did you give our date any more thought?
No, why would I do that?
Why not?
Saki, do you really hate me?
Or do you hate Mizuha?
Well, it's both
But why?
This is so awkward
You always say the first thing that comes to your mind
Mizuha's the opposite
That's why I don't like you
Bye!
But, hey!
Here
Take this
Huh?
If I give you this, then does that mean we can be friends?
Of course not, weirdo!
Hey!
This is for you
Uh, why?
Because if I give it to you, we can be friends
Uh-huh!
If anything, it freaks me out that you would think something like that would work
But don't you think it'd be better if we were friends?
Friends?
Don't forget, you left us
And I stayed with everyone else
That's all it is
Forget about all this friendship stuff
It's about where you belong
Now, I belong over there
Oh, but wait!
Don't leave without taking this hair accessory
Mizuha made it for you
For me?
Uh, yeah!
For you!
This was made for you, Nagisa!
Wow, huh?
Creepy
Kasube!
This is for you
Doesn't Mizuha always wear this thing?
Yeah!
She said you could have it
Why are you even doing this?
You talked more shit about Mizuha than any of us
And now you've become our best buddy?
Oh
Maybe I was only pretending to hate her
You're only pretending to, right?
What?
Shut up!
You don't know what you're saying!
Do you want this?
Mizuha made it
Oh, hey, Tonari
Hmm?
I see you got one of those as well
Huh?
Uh
She didn't want it at first
But she kept it for me
Right?
We both got one of them as well
You made these by hand, didn't you, Mizuha?
I love mine!
Thank you
Huh?
Who gave you them?
We got them from Funa
Here you go
Come here
Oh, Mizuha!
All of the first years love the hair accessory
Just come with me now
Having fun, are we, Fushi?
What do you think you're doing in that body?
Well, I haven't been able to get your family back yet
So I thought I could do something about your school life instead
I don't know what you're talking about
I just wanted to create a safe space for you
A place where you could be happy
So that you wouldn't think about wanting to die anymore
You were trying to create a place where I could be happy?
And you thought that it'd work by giving out these things
And lying to everyone in the school that I made them?
Oh, well, I probably should have done something else
I must have offended you and everyone who I gave the accessory to by lying about it
But you did all of this because you truly care about me
So much that you took over Funa's body for my sake
You became her all for me
I appreciate it
It's almost like you finally accepted me and the knockers and everything
You know, I never thought I would hear you talk about the knockers in that kind of way
Are you really Mizuha?
Or are you the knocker just pretending to be her?
Can't you tell?
Of course I'm Mizuha
That day when you rejected me
Funa's knocker told me about everything
Everything about the knockers who are inside us
Then when I got home
My left hand started moving on its own
When I showed it to mom and dad
They seemed so happy with me
It made me realize
That I really am special after all
I see
It looks like they've corrupted your mind as well
I'm sorry
I couldn't save you
But I'm gonna keep on trying for a little while longer
You should have the experience of enduring your own pain
And not have a knocker doing it all for you
Maybe that's why I hate the knockers
But that's not the only reason
I... I just think
Having a knocker take the pain on your behalf
It just doesn't seem right
It feels like you still haven't accepted yourself
It's like...
Like you put a bandage over a wound that never fully healed
I think you've never really recovered from the things that hurt you
It's really no big deal
The knockers are nothing more than flu medicine
They take the pain away for you
That's really it
No big deal
If that's the case then you won't mind if I remove that knocker then
Oh... I don't know about that
But if you're going to make me feel better instead then sure
Of course
If I can make that happen
Then I'll do my best
Then do it now
I don't mind if you're suggesting I'll be completely controlled
By you
Oh wow
I didn't know you were such a horndog, Mizuha
And I always thought you were so prim and proper
What?
Wait
What was I...
Why am I here?
Apologize
I want you to apologize for killing me
Sure
Maybe I did feel like dying
And yeah
Maybe I was talking shit about you
So it wasn't like
I didn't want to die
But that doesn't mean you should have just murdered me
I'm sorry but
I'm not the one who actually killed you
Oh
You're talking about those knocker things?
So you do have one in you
It sure looked like you enjoyed having it do everything for you
Like it was blissful
I was watching everything
You were watching?
Yeah
Because I was a ghost
I could see right into your room
You said some terrible things
And I learned all kinds of crazy stuff
But honestly it really wasn't all that bad
There were surprises
And happy moments
Don't forget that there are people out there who are worried about you
Even if they don't say it, okay?
It turns out my life didn't suck enough that I needed somebody to kill me after all
I'm glad I died so I can learn them
But that's not to say I'm actually grateful to you for killing me
If you won't apologize then how about this?
Why don't we chat once in a while?
Not as friends but because we both know each other's darkest secrets
We'll have plenty to talk about
But if you don't want to I get it
Shake on it
Oh, Mizuha
How's that?
I got her pretty good, didn't I?
Got her?
Yeah
I thought you brought me back to life because you wanted my help
No
I brought you back to life so you wouldn't be taken
What's that?
Whatever it means it sounds lovely
I'm really sorry
I feel like I got you mixed up in all this
Oh no
It's fine
I messed things up again
After all that effort
It got me nowhere in the end
Hey
Do you mind if I get that hair accessory, Funa?
Oh
Here's one
Sorry
Will this one work?
Yeah, it's great
So listen, I'm sorry for shouting at you earlier
Oh, it's okay
Don't worry about it
But I know
You can make up for it by inviting me over
We can talk about guys and stuff or whatever
Sure
And you thought that it worked by giving out these things?
Oh, so this is where you've been hiding, huh?
Are you okay?
About earlier
If it's okay with you, I'd still really like to be your friend
And if we're friends, I'd like you to tell me what you've been hiding from me
Wait a minute
You already left someone else, don't you?
I mean, it's not that we're both girls
It's just
But it's you
Hana, I love you
And don't you love me too?
Well, yeah
I guess I do, but it's
So it's okay then, right?
Well, I don't really know about that
You mean it that way, right?
Who knows what I mean?
I wonder
Wanna do it again?
You're acting weird
I thought you had feelings for Fushi
Why do you think that?
I mean, it's pretty obvious
I'm sorry if I made you jealous
But I don't like him
Truth is, Fushi's the one who likes me
Oh, really? He does?
I mean, I could tell you were on his mind quite a lot, but...
And what makes you so sure?
Just what I saw
You can do better than that
I saw how he acted
Just today
And at school
Or more like I hurt him, I guess
Sounds like the kind of thing Yuki would do, I suppose
Yuki knows
He's aware
He does?
He already knows?
It seems like everybody is worried about me
Because deep down they all really love me
Mizuha
Are you sure you're okay?
I just want you to be happy
So if there's anything I can do to help
Just let me know
All right
If you want to make me happy
Can I be your number one?
What does that mean?
My number one?
Like a trophy?
No
Oh, sorry
I don't really get it though
Do you realize just how incredibly plain, dull, and boring you are?
I mean, that's why you created that weird handicrafts club all by yourself
I'd think someone like you would be more than happy to have an amazing friend like me
Oh, is that how you feel?
Of course
Isn't that how you felt too?
Wow, Hana
You're great at that
Oh, thanks
You can have this one if you like it, Mizuha
Thanks, but I want that one
Huh?
Well, you know, it's my birthday today
Oh, is it really?
Come on
Let me have that one, pretty please
Wow, you really want it
If you insist
Okay
Consider this your birthday gift
Thank you
Yay
It's too flashy for me anyway
But I'm sure it'll suit you
I can't believe that the prettiest and smartest girl in our class
Is actually being super friendly to me
How does it look?
It looks great
I don't think I could feel any happier
Screw this
No, Hana, please just wait
Oh, she
Oh
Today's almost over
I've got to get back to work tomorrow
Gotta beat the knockers
But how?
Huh?
Hey, Mimory
It's been a while
Oh, hi, Fushi
How's Hirotoshi holding up?
The Foundation people put lots and lots of needles in him
And now he's all better
Oh yeah, good to hear
Oh, what you working on?
It's a secret skill
Attention grab no jutsu
If you make one and show it off
Then people respect you
And you get popular
You see?
Hirotoshi taught me how to do it
Can you teach me how to make one?
Okay
How are things at school?
Getting along with the kids?
Everything's gone back to normal
Back to normal?
Yeah
Hey, Mimory
Let's play dodgeball
Huh?
What's wrong?
You're being all weird
She's just staring
She's changed again
Aw
I liked her a lot better the other way
Since I went back to being myself again
Everybody has started ignoring me
Like they used to before
How are things with your mother now?
Nothing's changed with her either
I see
But I feel that it's all okay
I feel that I can give it my all this time
Can you tell me what I have to do
To be as strong as you are?
Strong as me?
Well, I don't think I'm strong at all
But you seem to be doing so much better now
From what I can see
In that case, I'm glad
That the knocker decided to take my body
You're glad?
Yes
If the knocker hadn't taken my body in the first place
Then I would have died that day at school
After jumping off the roof
Well, I guess
But
Let's start over
Wait, I don't understand
The knocker tried to use your body
That isn't true
Because I was using the knocker
I used it and I won
There, it's all done
Wow, it's so shiny
I bet March would be blown away by it
I wonder
What she's been up to
And didn't you say you won't return home
Until you wipe them all out
So will that be in 200 years
Or 400 years
Who is March?
Oh, March is part of my
Family
Does that mean she's your sister?
No, she's more like
Like my mother
Oh, so you call your mom by her name?
I guess you could say my family's a bit weird
Like Gugu, for example
He always wears a mask
Who is Gugu?
I guess you could say
That he's my big brother
You'd be surprised if you saw him
I have friends who live with me, too
And so do my
I guess you could call them co-workers
That sounds fun
I hope everyone
Is happy now
Hey, Mimory
Time to go home
Got to go
Okay
What about you?
Are you enjoying your life at home?
I'm going to start making it enjoyable
Look at this, Mom
What is that?
Did you find it?
I made it
It's a mud ball
Yeah?
Well, don't bring it inside
It's dirty
BUSHI!
Mnizuha?
I think Hana might hate me
Did I
Did I do something bad?
Well, what happened?
I
I don't know
I can't say
Okay, then
Whatever it was
You shouldn't blame yourself, alright?
BUSHI
You really are too kind, you know?
Well, you'll be okay
I'm sure everything will be just fine
Oh, that's right
Hold out your hand
Huh?
You can have this
I only just made it
Although it's not very good
What is this?
Attention grab no jutsu
See?
If you learn to make one
Then you can offer one to Hana
And make up with her
Huh?
It's kind of late today
So I can teach you how to make it another day
Bye
Oh
Hang on, Fushi
I really don't think that this will work
Fushi, hang on!
This doesn't solve anything!
Uh-huh
I'm still crying
Haven't you noticed my tears?
Yeah
What do you mean, yeah?
Then why are you walking away?
I'm sorry, but
What do you want me to do?
March, I'm back home
Check this out
Wow, what is this thing?
It's so shiny
It's a mud ball
Did you make this by yourself, Fushi?
That's right, March
I'll teach you how to make one too
Then it'll make you super popular
Will you really?
Thank you so much, Fushi
I'm so happy
Don't hate me
I couldn't stand it if you did
Okay, see you tomorrow
But where are you going?
I'm going home, where else?
The Knockers live inside those who are eager to die
That's what the Knockers said
There's so much fun in this world
Plenty of sturdy homes
So much good food to eat
There really isn't any time to be sad
So then, why would someone want to die?
I feel like it's something I won't ever be able to understand
Especially in this world
I'm sure March and Gugu and everyone else would agree
That this world is much better
Than the one where they were always exhausted from fighting
I'm home, everybody!
Welcome home, Fushi!
Why is it so quiet around here?
Kai made his workshop
I'm so happy for him
And there's Gugu's workout stuff
Isn't this...
Huh?
Are you okay?
Who are you?
Wake up!
Echo?
March!
What happened?
Huh?
No...
Mo?
What's Novo mean?
I don't understand!
Maipon!
Go-goo!
Is anyone here?
Tanari!
Would you mind keeping it down?
What's with all the screaming the second you get home?
It's March and Echo!
I don't know what's happened!
Just calm down
A tutor has been teaching them how to hold chopsticks and write and stuff
Huh?
Oh...
So she was trying to write no more
Well, if you're done here, I'm really trying to study
You're studying?
Did you forget we have finals next week?
A final?
What's that mean?
I hope that you understand that you can't make blades without a permit
Do you hear me?
What is this?
Don't let us catch you doing it again
Whoa, Go-goo!
And Hiro!
What's happened to everybody?
I don't think that anyone is really happy
Dism
What's happened to everybody?
I don't know!
But now it doesn't really matter, let us show you tomorrow
What's happened to everybody?
believed to be
Need to see more
What are the statements here?
We'll be right back.